Hello friends, in this video I will
tell you the easiest way to download ICICI Bank's loan
statement and loan difference.
Friends, there are two options here. The
first option is if you have a
savings account in this bank, then you
can download it through net banking. The second
option is to download the iMobile application.
Go to the Play Store and
type 'iMobile'. It will appear and appear to you.
Install it
on your phone. This video is also for those people
who do not have any savings account in the ICC bank,
only the loan is active in ICC Bank. As
soon as you open it, friends, it
asks for some permissions. Whatever permission it
asks for, you should not give that permission.
Like, it asks for permission for phone calls.
I will set it aside. It will run for a while.
Friends, it will appear here in this manner. Let
it run and as soon as it is completed,
you will get this page. Here,
click on the blue colored strip written 'Let's Get Started'.
After that, you have to click on the Indian President Account here and continue.
Now, after this, if you have a referral code, then
report it to me.  Have a different, you
can click here, if you want, you can continue
this, after that you have to select the SIM card
which is registered with your ICICI Bank, so you can
understand me, I select this and continue,
after this it will
run for a little while, here the messages and songs will start on your phone
and
[music], it
reads all those messages automatically, now after this you have to
set a four digit PIN,
you can set any four digit PIN here
and after that click OK,
friends, here you enter the four
digit login PIN, whatever PIN you have created,
type it here, now
after that friends, if you want, you
can put a fingerprint lock in it,
brother, do this, I am doing this
and after that, this continue which is visible, keep continuing, the
next process is completed,
cut the power, after cutting, here
friends, I have just highlighted the summary here, the
boys in the skin  The details
are visible and this More option is the third
job
option. More options, if you click
from here MI Schedule
Statement Account, click on it, the
statement of account will be entered
and if you want customer care
number, you will
get this customer care number by clicking on contact here.
Friends, let me tell you that I have
uploaded videos on loan statements of all major banks,
so subscribe to the channel. If any
kind of update comes, if any new option
comes, then I will make a video on that too
and if anyone wants to take a loan, then you
can contact me. I will meet you again
with the video. Friends, Jai Hind, thank you.